English together
英语一起学
Ordering at a coffee shop. Good morning. Can I get a coffee, please?
在咖啡店点单。早上好，可以给我来杯咖啡吗？
Good morning
早上好。
Absolutely
当然没问题。
What type of coffee would you like? I'll have a cappuccino, please
您要什么类型的咖啡呢？我要一杯卡布奇诺。
medium-sized if possible
如果有的话，中杯的。
sure thing
好的，没问题。
Would you like it for here or to go? I'll have it to go, please
是堂食还是外带呢？请帮我打包带走吧。
Alright anything else
还需要别的吗？
Actually, can I also get a chocolate chip muffin of?
其实我还想再要一个巧克力豆玛芬。
Course one chocolate chip muffin anything else
一份巧克力豆玛芬，还有别的吗？
Just the cappuccino and the muffin, please
就是卡布奇诺和玛芬，谢谢。
Alright, that will be eight dollars
好的，一共八美元。
cash or card
现金还是刷卡呢？
I'll pay with card, please
我用信用卡支付。
Here's your receipt
这是你的收据
Your order will be ready in just a few minutes
你点的餐几分钟就好了
Great. Thank you
太好了，谢谢
Thanks for watching if you enjoyed this video, please give it a like and consider subscribing to my channel for more content like this
如果你喜欢这个视频，请点赞并考虑订阅我的频道以获取更多类似内容